Guide to the John N. Warfield papers, 1931-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Textual Materials, 1943-2001; (51 boxes)
  - Budget Files, Budget Processes & Budget Operations, [Center for Interactive Management, 1987-1990] (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Association for Integrative Studies Conference & Other Related Material", November 4. 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "Total Quality Management (TQM)& Other Related Material," [Correspondence], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Clausing [Don], Laboratory for Manufacturing & Productivity, MIT," [Correspondence], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "Brucheum Group," An International Organization of Technical & Management Consultants", 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Correspondence Bob McDonald [GMU Administration], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Christakis & Associates," [Alexander Christakis], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "LBJ School of Public Affairs" University of Texas, Austin [Correspondence], 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "India" [Various Correspondents], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "Modeling & Analysis of Management Information System Architecture at National Level," [M.P.Gupta], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "Netherlands" [Various Correspondence], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "Poland" [Various Correspondence], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - "England" [Various Correspondence], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "Cognitive Equilibrium," [Dr. Milan Zeleny], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "GMU - The Institute of Public Policy," [Correspondence With Administration Offices], 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "GMU - The Institute of Public Policy," [Correspondence With Administration Offices], 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - "GMU - The Institute of Public Policy," [Correspondence With Administration Offices], 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "GMU - The Institute of Public Policy," [Correspondence With Administration Offices], 1986-1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - "Cognitive Equilibrium & Human Systems Management", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - "Mexico - ITESM," [Correspondence with Roxana Cardenas], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - "ITESM Mexico," Brochures, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "Mexico," [Correspondence with Lopez Matus], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - "Operation Budgets - IASIS," George Mason University, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - "Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation" [Correspondence], 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "Nashville Operations," [Cliff Saunders, Correspondence], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - "Shared Memory in Design," Engineering Design Research Center, Carnegie Mellon University, [E. Swaran Subrahmanian, Philip Sargent, Ira Monarch], October 1991 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - "Research in Engineering Design: An Organizational Framework for Design Theories," [Norman L. Fortenberry] Carnegie Mellon, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - "Austria," [Correspondence Regarding European Meeting on Cybernetics & Systems Research], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - [Miscellaneous Correspondence One], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - [Miscellaneous Correspondence Two], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "Center for Nuclear Waste Regulatory Analyses Correspondence with Bob Adler", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "Issues in Integrative Studies," [Correspondence Julie Klein], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - "Clausing Don, MIT Labs, Correspondence with John N. Warfield", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "Lucy Reilly, Washington Technology, Correspondence with John N. Warfield", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - "Correspondence Dave Mackett & Warfield", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - "Interactive Management Consultants," Christakis Correspondence with John N. Warfield", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "Christakis Correspondence with John N. Warfield", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - "Li D. Xu, Wright State University Correspondence About Systems Research with John N. Warfield", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - "Brazil, Correspondence with Wright", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - "Roxana Cardenas, Correspondence with Warfield", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Ghana, Correspondence with Dr M.N.B Ayiku About ISM Related Material", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - "Japan" [Various Correspondents], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - "International Conference on Engineering Design" Zurich, [Correspondence with Dr. Hubak], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - "Poland [Various Correspondents], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - "Greece [Correspondence with Kapelouzos] Regarding System Research", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - "India" [Various Correspondents], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - "England" [Various Correspondents], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - "Netherlands" [Correspondence], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - "Germany" [Correspondence with Kornwacks], undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - "Visiting Scholar GU, Kaiping, Beijing Forestry University", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - "Graphics Representations Glossary, Words," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "Graphics Representations Glossary, Words," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Graphics Representations Glossary, Drafts & Notes," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "Switching Networks as Models of Discrete Stochastic Processes, in Applied Automata Theory," [Julius T. Tou, John N. Warfield], 1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Planning to Meet Educational Needs of Ohio Schools.Phase-I & II, Summary Report," Ohio Department of Education, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "Graphics Representations Glossary, Draft #2," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Graphics Representations Glossary, Rough Draft & Notes," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Graphics Representations Glossary, Draft #2," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Development of a Unified Systems Engineering Approach," [John N. Warfield], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "What is System Planning?," [John N. Warfield, R. W. House], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Digital Squelch System - Patent," [John N. Warfield], 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Modulation Measurements - Theory & Technique," IEEE / Instruments & Measurements, June 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Research Notes on Braybrooke & Lindblom", 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "The Delta Chart: A Method for R & D Project Portrayal," [John N. Warfield, J.D. Hill], 1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - "Systems Planning in Guidelines for Improving Project Management," IV - 1 & IV - 11, A Report for Ohio Department of Education, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "The Gold Book," Developing Improved Methods for Dealing With Complex Societal Problems, November 1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Participate Methodology for Public System Planning," Presented at International Symposium on Systems Engineering & Analysis, Purdue University, October 23, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "A Unified Systems Engineering Approach," Battelle Monograph, June 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Preliminary Specifications for a Computer System to Augment the ISM Process", 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Science Base for Societal Problem Research," Battelle Quarterly Report Article, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Intent Structures," [John N. Warfield], IEEE Article, March 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "On Arranging Elements of a Hierarchy in Graphic Form," [John N Warfield], March 1973 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "An Assault on Complexity," Battelle Monograph #3, Slides Used for Illustration, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - "An Assault on Complexity," Battelle Monograph #3, April 1973 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "Unified Program Planning," [J. Douglas Hill, John N. Warfield], November 1972 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "The Islands of E, Cono and My," [Simon Ramo] Reviewed by John N. Warfield, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - "An Assault on Complexity," Permission Letters From Battelle Monograph, April 1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Binary Matrices in System Modeling," IEEE/SMC-3, [John N. Warfield], September 1973 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - "Constructing Operational Value Systems for Proposed Two-Unit Coalitions," [John N. Warfield], December 5, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - "An Interim Look at Uses of Interpretive Structural Modeling", 1974 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - "Developing Subsystem Matrices in Structural Modeling," [John N. Warfield], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - "Developing Interconnection Matrices in Structural Modeling," [John N. Warfield], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - "Urban Systems Methodology," [John N. Warfield], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - "Structuring Complex Systems" Battelle Monograph #4, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - "Towards Interpretation of Complex Structural Models", September 1974 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - "Modularization of Large Econometric Models," [John N. Warfield], 1974 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #1 [John N. Warfield], March 26, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #2 [John N. Warfield], April 19, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #3 [John N. Warfield], June 1, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #4, [John N. Warfield], July 26, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #5, [John N. Warfield], August 25, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #6, [John N. Warfield], October 11, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #9, Part One, [John N. Warfield], February 15, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #9, Part Two, [John N. Warfield], February 15, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," Draft #9, [John N. Warfield], February 20, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - An Updated Preface Written for "A Structure Based Science of Complexity," [John N. Warfield], September 2000 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - "City University, Technical Report: Product Services & Priorities for the Engineering Industry Training Board, November 1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "City University, Technical Report: Setting Priorities for Highway Schemes in Hertfordshire Using ISM ", May 1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "Technical Report: Planning Exercise for the Management Support Department," City University, May 1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Technical Report: Requirements & Priorities for a Community Speech Therapy Service," City University, August 1988 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Technical Report: Model 1: Linen Services, Computer Modeling Application," City University, September 1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "Technical Report: Objectives & PRIORITIES FOR THE ACCOMMODATIONS & CONFERENCE SERVICE," City University, February 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "Centro de Estudios Strategicos, ITESM, [Empty], undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - "Ellis, Naeyaert, Geniheimer Associates & Friedman, Conceptual Floor Plan," [Empty], undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "Rough Draft Summary of Tentative Needs for 1992 Demosophia in Dearborn," [Benjamin Broome], October 1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "Contract Negotiations in an Electronic Meeting Room, Case Studies," [Nunamaker Jay, Erran Carmrl, Bruce C. Hermoter], August 20, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - "Floor Plan for George Mason University Situation Room," CIM, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "Floor Plan for Situation Room," Tentative Plan, CIM, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - "Format & Production of Bound Reports for Clients," Center for Interactive Management, October 1987 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Major Physical Design Factors in Creating a Demosophia: A 1987 Memo," CIM, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - "Requirements for Creating a Temporary Off - Site Demosophia," CIM, September 1988 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - "Defense Systems Management College (DSMC) Design Facility Workshop", October 1999 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - "Estimate of Probable Construction Cost," Ellis,Nawyaert, Genheimer Associates Inc., September 1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - "Implementing Electronic Meeting Systems at IBM: Lessons Learned & Success Factors," [Ron Grohowski, Chris McGoff], December 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - "Demosophia - 1984 Draft: Cost Estimate," [Keever David], October 1992 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "Proposed AIIM FAcility - 1989, Draft," [Keever David], October 1992 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - "Doe Beryllium Rule Creation, an Application of Complexity Solutions," IM Report, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - "The Southwest Fisheries Science Center, Situation Room," [Raymond Ken], February 1984 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - "Newspaper Clipping: Judge Lance Ito sat Here of O.J. Simpson Trial", March 15, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - "Electronic Meeting System Experience at IBM," [Vogel, Nunamaker, McGoff], 1989 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - "A Structure Based Science of Complexity: An Index of Drafts," [John N. Warfield], February 2000 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Plague, Organizations in Complexity," [William Livingstone], September 4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "The New Plague, Organizations in Complexity," [William Livingstone], December 1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "Design for Improving University/Industry Cooperative Research Projects," [David B. Keever], undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "Facilitating Group Communication: The Interactive Management Approach," [David B. Keever, Benjamin Broome], May 3, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "Towards an Intellectual Base in Theory of Conflict Resolution," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "Pragmatics of Database Management, Outline of the Panel Discussion," [Edgar H. Silbey], 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "The Four Competencies of Leadership," [Richard Beyea], April 25, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "A Complexity Metric for High Level Software Language," [John N. Warfield], July 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Correspondence About Computer Science Mathematics Curriculum," [John Dixon], Program Director of NSF, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "Newspaper Clippings & Articles of Robert Waller", undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - "Decision Making for Leaders, Multicriterion Decisions in Systems with Feedback," [Thomas L. Sasty], undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "Conflict Management Related Material", 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "Conflict Management Related Material", 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - "Center for Interactive Management, University of Virginia [Various Correspondents], 1983 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "Center for Interactive Management, University of Virginia [Various Correspondents], 1984 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Correspondence with Richard Beyea III ", 1985 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - "Center for Interactive Management, University of Virginia [Various Correspondents], 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "Chronology of Center for Interactive Management Activities at George Mason University," [John N. Warfield], Director of Institute for Information Technology, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - "Various Correspondents with John N. Warfield", 1987 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - "Various Correspondents About Systems Research, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "Systems Research Journal Papers," Editor in Chief Dr. John N. Warfield, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - "Correspondence About ISM with [Faqir Kohli, G.S. Chandy]", 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - "Miscellaneous Material," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "Books Sent to Binding, List of Titles & Correspondence", 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - "Cartoon Poster Which John N. Warfield had Attached to his Office Door at 217 Thompson Hall", 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - "University of Michigan - Dearborn Correspondence Regarding Systems Engineering Course With Prof. P.K. Mallick", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "[Various Correspondents] Regarding System Design", undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "Correspondence with Dr. Vassilis Morfopoulos", April 1989 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - "Ten Year Service Pin & Certificate Issued by State of Virginia, George Mason University Faculty Honors Assembly", April 8, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - "Statue of Liberty, Ellis Island Centennial Commission Certificate," [Mr. & Mrs. John N. Warfield], undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - "Newspaper Clippings & Articles on George Mason University", 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - "IASIS & CIM Activities Related Papers", 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - "Various Correspondents in 1984" (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - "Correspondence Related to Alexander Christakis", 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - "Correspondence Related to Alexander Christakis", 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - "Thoughts on Software Productivity & Task Statement," [Edgar H. Sibley, James D. Palmer], undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - "Correspondence Between Alexander Christakis & John N. Warfield", undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - "Interactive Management Facilitation & Programs in India," Correspondence [Faqit Kohli, Yamina Prabhu, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - "Information Technology / Interactive Management Facilitation & Programs", 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - "Center for Interactive Management Activities With North Pacific Fisheries Forum & Other Related Materials", 1985 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - "Correspondence Between John N. Warfield & Myron Tribus", 1985 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - "NSF Funding & Establishment of NSF Center in Knowledge Support System Design & Human Machine Interaction," George Mason, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - "Correspondence with Andrew P. Sage Dean of School of Information Technology & Dr John N. Warfield About (DOD) Department of Defense Proposals", 1985 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - "Correspondence With Andrew P. Sage Dean of School of Information Technology & Dr John N. Warfield", 1985 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - "Information Research & Projects & Correspondence", 1983-1988 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - "Education Papers by John N. Warfield: A Collection of Writings," [John N. Warfield], 1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "The Wandwaver Solution," Backup Copy of Volume 7 of Education Papers," [John N. Warfield], 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Education Papers by Warfield," Backup Copy of Volume 6 [John N. Warfield], 1968-19996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "Education Papers by Warfield," Backup Copy of Volume 4 [John N. Warfield], 1968-1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Education Papers by Warfield," Backup Copy of Volume 5 [John N. Warfield], 1968-1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Education Papers by Warfield," Backup Copy of Volume 3 [John N. Warfield], 1968-1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "Education Papers by Warfield," Backup Copy of Volume 1 [John N. Warfield], 1968-1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "Education Papers by Warfield," Backup Copy of Volume 2 [John N. Warfield], 1968-1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "A Course in Generic Design for Engineers (1995 Version)," [John N. Warfield], undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - "A Course in Generic Design for Engineers, Correspondence with Publishers," [John N. Warfield], 1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "The Delta Chart: Using Interactive Management to Construct Delta Charts," [John N. Warfield], 1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "Demands Imposed on Higher Education by Complexity," Presented at Colloquium of the Institute of Public Policy, George Mason University, April 1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Demands Imposed on Research & Writing by Complexity," [Dr. John N. Warfield, Dr. Scott Staley], 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Demands of Complexity on Higher Education," Seminar Presented at George Mason University, March 1995 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Demands Imposed on Systems Science by Complexity," [John N. Warfield], July 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "Demands of Complexity on Systems Science," Session Talk, May 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "Demands of Complexity on Systems Science," Plenary Session Address, Presented at IV Annual Meeting of United Kingdom Systems Society, July 1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "An Essay on Complexity," [John N. Warfield], September 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "Four Books on Complexity: Summaries," [John N. Warfield], October 1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "Four Case Studies: Applications of Interactive Management," Presented at Fourth European School of Systems, U.K., July 1995 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "The Great University: A George Mason University Faculty Seminar," Presented at Mason Hall, George Mason University, October 26, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Index to George J. Friedman Constraint Theory Applied to Mathematical Model Consistency & Computational Allowablitiy" Dissertation from University of California, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "Procrustes is Alive & Well & Teaching Composition in the English Department," Presented at 17th Annual Meeting, Arizona, September 1995 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "A Philosophy of Design," Presented at First World Conference on Integrated Design, University of Texas, Austin, December 1995 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "A Panel of Philosophers & A Poet," Presented at United States F.D.A., Maryland, April 1995 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - "On Redesigning of the Joint Panning & Execution Program", 1995 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - "The Multiform Calendar," [John N. Warfield], 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - "Memtomology: Identification & Classification of Mindbugs," [John N. Warfield], 1995 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - "Interpretation of Problematique for Policy Research," [John N. Warfield], January 13, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - "Comparing IM Methods Widely Used in Japan. Chapter 14 in a Handbook of Interactive Management" [John N. Warfield, Roxana Cardenas], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - "Comments on Two Future Related World Issues" [John N. Warfield], March 1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - "Clanthink: Assures Institutionalized Mediocrity, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - "Case Study in Conflict Management in Concurrent Engineering: Ford Motor Company Experience," [John N. Warfield, Staley, Scott], July 1994 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - "The IASIS File: A Bibliography of Books & Papers Relevant to Organization & Design," [John N. Warfield], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - "A Handbook of Interactive Management, Second Edition," Correspondence with Publisher, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - "Cybernetics (Encyclopedia Article)", 1994 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - "Complexity: A Subject of Inequity," [John N. Warfield], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - "Some Lessons Learned From a Quarter of a Century of Research on Complexity," [John N. Warfield], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - "Publications on Complexity," [John N. Warfield], July 1994 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - "Prolog to a Science of Complexity," Draft #1 [John N. Warfield], December 1994 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - "Prolog to a Science of Complexity," Draft #1 [John N. Warfield], December 1994 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - "Origins & Remedies for Situational Complexity in Organizations," [John N. Warfield], 1994 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - "Structural Thinking & Interactive Management: A Short Course," George Mason University, June 1994 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - "Transfer of Interactive Management Technology to Ford Motor Company," [John N. Warfield], August 1994 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - "Complexity & Drummers: A Manual for a Five Day Course," George Mason University, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - "Trends of Systems Science & Technology", 1994 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - "A Compressed History of Development of ISM, Science of Complexity, Science of Generic Design & Interactive Management," [John N. Warfield], June 1995 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - "Photographs of Situation Rooms & IM Workshop Sessions," Demosophia, George Mason University, June 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Photographs of Situation Rooms & IM Workshop Sessions: Jopes Workshop, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - "RRM Workshop Photographs at Ford Motor Company," Dearborn, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "Photographs from Product Information Management Systems (PIM) Workshop at Ford Motor Company", January 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "Photographs: IM Workshop at Ford Motor Company", 1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - "Photographs: Naval Surface Weapons Center IM Session", 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - "Photographs: Demosophia at George Mason University in 1980's," Fairfax, VA, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)